Fadillah Fahrudin

Designer & Front-End Developer

As a young man aged 25 years, has experience as a junior web developer in a social institution (Semangat Bantu) for 1 year, has experience in making donation applications using React Native which I present for final exams at Pamulang University and is proficient in design. I have a strong interest especially in front-end developer.

Contact

+62 812 8312 5735 fadilfahrudin32@gmail.com

Education

Pamulang University Bachelor Degree in Informatics Engineering, 3.04/4.00 IPK

Expertise

UI & Visual Design Graphic Design Front-End Enginner Video Editor

Tools & Technologies

HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Laravel Framework, React JS, React Native Library, Bootstrap Figma, Adobe Photoshop, After Effect and Final Cut Pro.

Languange

Indonesia (native) English (intermediate)

Courses

Responsive Web Design (Freecodecamp.org), Build Full-Stack Javascript Developer: Website Travel & React Native: Integration With REST API (CRUD) at buildwithangga.com

References

Teuku Ghalib Muadzan CEO Semangatbantu.com teukughalib@gmail.com

Zaini Miftah

CTO Semangatbantu.com edjie.miftah@gmail.com

Irwan Setiono

Designer Semangatbantu.com irwansetiyono9@gmail.com

Experience

Design Graphic

Yavasan Laiu Peduli Aug 2018 - Jun 2019

Make poster designs for social media (Instagram), print designs such as banners and other tools.

Content Creator & Social Media Specialist

Yavasan Laju Peduli Jun 2019 - Dec 2019

Make a design content and management of social media Laju Peduli with a mission to fundraise donations to help orphans and poor people.

Comunity Network

Semangatbantu.com Jul 2021 - Dec 2021

Invite a community from anywhere like an organization university or a public community to join our programs for cooperation to help so many people.

Junior Web Developer

Semangatbantu.com Jan 2022 - Jan 2023

Collaborate with senior developers and other divisions to meet technology-related needs, design website interfaces, slicing to HTML, CSS, Javascript and learning frameworks commonly used by foundations, one of which is the Laravel framework.

Skills, Achievement and Other Experience

Top 5 Logo Design

Jun 2021

Successfully entered the top 5 in participating in the logo competition held by Pamulang University for the new Sasmita Foundation logo.

React Native: Integration with REST API (CRUD)

Aug 2022

Certificate get from Build With Angga Class









